{
    "subject": "Alan_Alda",
    "predicate": "actedIn",
    "object": "The_Four_Seasons__film_",
    "human_readable": "Alan Alda acted in the film The Four Seasons.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9859236478805542,
            "question": "What role did Alan Alda play in 'The Four Seasons'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8677667379379272,
            "question": "Who acted in the film 'The Four Seasons'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8054063320159912,
            "question": "What film did Alan Alda act in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7922092080116272,
            "question": "In which film did Alan Alda star?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7723275423049927,
            "question": "What other movies has Alan Alda acted in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7642678022384644,
            "question": "Is Alan Alda an actor?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6949652433395386,
            "question": "Can you name a movie starring Alan Alda?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6506234407424927,
            "question": "What is the name of the film featuring Alan Alda?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5376124978065491,
            "question": "Has Alan Alda been in any films?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5124447345733643,
            "question": "Besides acting, what other roles has Alan Alda had?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Alan Alda acted in the film The Four Seasons.",
            "html": "yago_26395_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Has Alan Alda been in any films?",
            "html": "yago_26395_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of the film featuring Alan Alda?",
            "html": "yago_26395_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you name a movie starring Alan Alda?",
            "html": "yago_26395_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_26395_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_26395_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_26395_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_26395_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_26395_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_26395_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_26395_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_26395_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_26395_52.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_26395_55.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that Alan Alda wrote, directed, and starred in the film \"The Four Seasons\" released in 1981. Therefore, it is correct to state that Alan Alda acted in the film \"The Four Seasons.\""
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}